We are living through strange days.
Across Britain, Europe and America,
societies have become split
and polarised,
not just in politics,
but across the whole culture.
There is anger at the inequality
and the ever-growing corruption
and a widespread distrust
of the elites.
Yet, at the same time,
there is a paralysis,
a sense that no-one knows
how to escape from this.
Even in America, where there is now
hope with the new president,
there are also fears that,
despite the growing crisis,
the system will just return
to normal.
This paralysis is also fuelled
by a technology, driven by the aim
of giving you today another version
of what you had yesterday...
..and never a different tomorrow.
These films are a history
of how we got to this place